question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "On average, at least 1 person is killed by a drunk driver in the United States every hour.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "The end credits sequence in Grand Theft Auto 5 is over half an hour long.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"]}, {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In World War ll, Great Britian used inflatable tanks on the ports of Great Britain to divert Hitler away from Normandy\/D-day landing.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klaang is a typical Klingon male.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Art", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Leonardo da Vinci was not the creator of the Mona Lisa.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In &quot;Space Station 13&quot;,  the station has a clown aboard it.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
